# Robin LIN

Phone: 0413292200 | Email: robinlin526@gmail.com

#### SUMMARY =

An ex-surveyor with a wide exposure to general construction survey, cadastral survey, 3D scanning & spatial data processing. But seeking career steering to new roles to utilize GIS technical knowledge which has been proud of. After six-year higher education in spatial information and nearly three years of surveyor work, I have a comprehensive understanding of spatial information. Proficient in various spatial software especially ArcGIS and being able to utilize the most appropriate one and integration results. Always modest to learn new knowledge, to improve procedure of daily works and always fueled with passion.

#### - EDUCATION -

#### THE UNIVERSITY OF MELBOURNE

Master of Engineering (Spatial)

Melbourne, VIC Jul 2017 – July 2019

- Research Project: Automated texturing of historical BIMs case study of the Royal Exhibition Building
- Project involves techniques in BIM, drone images photogrammetry, and indoor 3D laser scanning.

TONGJI UNIVERSITY

Shanghai, China Sep 2013 – July 2017

Bachelor of Engineering in Surveying and Geo-informatics

- Research Project: Grassland livestock recognition and estimating in drone images using MATLAB
- DJI drone operation skill, programming and image processing techniques played roles in projects.
- Leaded the project Mobile Air Quality Monitoring System Based on Position: Published a website which demonstrates air quality data collected by monitors and visualized with Baidu MAP API.

## PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE =

**GEOSURV** 

Canberra, ACT

Surveyor

March 2021 – April 2022

- Managing survey works of a long list of landmark apartments, infrastructure projects and residential properties in Canberra independently.
- 3D scanning for commercial properties.

**MET SURVEYORS** 

Pilbara, WA

Surveyor

Jun 2020 – Nov 2020

- Engineering and construction survey in Rio Tinto, BHP & FMG mine sites: Underground Services, Earthworks, Road
  construction, Concrete, and Railways. Tasks including set-out and as-built for all kinds of infrastructures in mine site.
- Volume calculation with drone modelling.

### **RL SOLAR CONSTRUCTION**

Pilbara, WA

Surveyor

Apr 2020 – Jun 2020

- Setout out Solar panel supporting piles and provide as-built data analysis.
- Substation and electrical conduits as-built.
- Provide drone images for overall progress tracking.

# METRO SURVEY GROUP

Melbourne

Assistant Surveyor

May 2019 - Mar 2020

- Land survey for residential properties, land subdivision survey.
- Rural survey and interior survey.

## PROFESSIONAL SKILLS =

**Software:** ArcGIS Pro, QGIS, Envi, Civil3D, AutoCAD, Liscad, Metashape, Revit, FARO Scene **Proficient programming language:** Python, SQL, JavaScript, C#, VB.Net, Matlab, R

**Referees:** 

Robert Harman MET senior surveyor (manager) Mobile: 0419 318 384
Richard Ferguson Senior Surveyor in Geosurv (colleague) Mobile: 0423 426 571